# Lucas Fu

# Full-stack Web Engineer

high5dev621@gmail.com | Montreal, QC, Canada



#### Summary

I am a web developer with more than 10 years of extensive experience developing, optimizing, and supporting web applications.

My main goal is to find solutions that meet all clients' requests with a focus on timely delivery.

I believe that accuracy and honesty are the keys to successful cooperation.

#### Work experience

Full-stack Engineer

August 2020 - April 2022

#### Snakt

- Implemented both front-end and back-end core systems in the Agile software development team.
- Implemented complex UI components with React/TypeScript and SCSS and built from scratch admin platform using MERN stack.
- Resolved the high technical challenges to implement the business logic based on the client's requirements and specifications.
- Optimized the core project structure to build the website fast and easy.

Senior Web Developer

March 2019 - July 2020

#### Keenprint

- Developed an Angular, RxJS, and Angular Material web app for seminars and webinars hosting in GCP.
- Implemented an admin panel for internal staff to manage all the data and generate reports to monitor the usage.
- · Implemented user-friendly, interactive, pixel-perfect, and responsive UI.

Software Engineer

July 2018 - February 2019

#### Lembergk

- Developed a React, React hook, and Material UI front-end web app for a real estate tax calculation.
- Communicated using agile scrum methodology, conducting two-weeklong sprints, keeping the product shippable at all times.
- Worked closely with the product team to build new features for the desktop and mobile site.

Web Developer

July 2015 - June 2018

## Ragnarson

- Integrated Redux on a number of React-based front-end projects for the better state management of React components.
- Built many kinds of reusable UI components and data visualization components.
- · Created a new customized chart library using D3.js.
- · Integrated Vue.js, Vuex, and Vuetify with a Laravel back-end.

### Education

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science McGill University 2011 - 2015

Blockchain

